In this video we'll
put together everything we've learned
in the previous videos to
create an end-to-end example of a
customer service assistant. We'll go through
the following
steps. First, we'll check the input
to see
if it flags the moderation API.
Second, if it doesn't, we'll extract
the list of products. Third, if
the products are found, we'll try
to look them up.
And four, we'll answer the user question
with the model. And
finally, we'll put the answer through the
moderation API. And if
it is not flagged, we'll return it
to the user.
So we have our setup.
We have this additional import.
This is a Python package we'll
use for a chatbot UI.
And so I'm
going to paste in a function "process_user_message".
And I'm actually going to
run an example first and
then we'll talk through the function.
So we have our user input that we've
been using. Tell
me about the smartx pro
phone and the camera. Also
tell me about TVs.
So let's run this.
First, let's run this.
So as you can see, we're
going through the steps to
answer the user question.
So the first step,
the moderation step,
the second step is
extracting the list of products.
The third step is
looking up the product information.
And so now with this product
information, the model is trying to
answer the question as we've
seen in the previous videos.
And then finally,
it puts the response
through the moderation API
again to make sure it's
safe to show to the user.
And so this is the response that we're
now familiar with.
And so let's
talk through a little bit of what's happening.
So we have our helper function
"process_user_message".
It takes in the user input,
which is the current message,
and an array of all of the messages
so far and this is when we build
the chatbot UI. So the first step,
checking to see if the
input flags the moderation API.
We covered this in a previous video.
If the input is flagged,
then we tell the user that we can't
process the request.
If it is not flagged,
we try to extract the
list of products as we
did in the previous video.
Then we try to look up the products.
And in this case,
if no products are found,
this will just be an empty string.
Then we answer the user question,
so we give the conversation history
and the new messages with the
relevant product information.
So we get the response,
and then we run this
response through the moderation API.
If it's flagged, we
tell the user that we can't provide
this information. Maybe we'll
say something like, let me connect
you, and you could take some subsequent
step.
And so, let's
put this all together with a nice UI, and
try to have a conversation.
So here we have
a function that will
just accumulate the messages
as we interact with the assistant.
And feel free to pause
the video to understand in
more detail how this works.
And of course feel free to
do the same for the really long
"process_user_message" function that
we just saw as well.
So now we're going to paste in our code
to display the chatbot UI.
So if we run this, now let's
try and have a conversation with
the customer service assistant.
So let's ask, "what TVs do you have".
And under the hood,
the assistant is going through
all of the steps in the "process_user_message"
function.
So it's
listed a variety of different TVs. So
now let's ask, "which is
the cheapest".
Again, it's
going through all the same steps, but
this time it's passing
the conversation history as well
into the prompts.
Okay, so it's telling us that this
speaker is the cheapest
TV related product we have.
Interesting. Let's
see what the most expensive is.
So the most expensive TV
is the CineView 8K TV.
So let's
ask for more information about it, "tell
me more about it".
And so we've received some more information
about this television.
So in this example, we've
combined the techniques we've learned
throughout the course to create a
comprehensive system with
a chain of steps that evaluates
user inputs, processes them,
and then
checks the output.
By monitoring the quality
of the system across
a larger number of inputs,
you can alter the
steps and improve the
overall performance of your system.
Maybe we might find that
our prompts could be better
for some of the steps,
maybe some of the steps aren't
even necessary. Maybe we'll find
a better retrieval method, and so
on. We'll discuss this
more in the next video.